<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addons>

<addon id="repository.orphaned-add-ons" name="Orphaned add-ons repo" version="1.0" provider-name="host505">
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Orphaned add-ons repo">
    <dir>
        <info compressed="false">https://github.com/host505/orphaned-add-ons/raw/master/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://github.com/host505/orphaned-add-ons/raw/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/host505/orphaned-add-ons/master/</datadir>
    </dir>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>Home for orphaned Kodi add-ons</summary>
        <description>Home for orphaned Kodi add-ons</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="context.subtitlesdialog.contextmenu" name="Subtitles Dialog - Contextmenu" version="1.0.1" provider-name="burekas">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.20.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="kodi.context.item" library="addon.py">
      <item>
        <label>32000</label>
        <visible>true</visible>
      </item>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Adds a subtitles dialog contextmenu button</summary>
        <description lang="en">Adds a subtitles dialog contextmenu button to context menu, so you can use the subtitles dialog also when kodi is not playing.[CR]You can use the manual search button to check if subtitles exist, or focus on an item and it will automatically check it for you without typing.[CR][CR]Only supported by these addons and above:[CR]Subscenter.org (4.1.2)[CR]Ktuvit.com (4.5.1)[CR]TheWiz Subs (1.1.4)[CR]Torec (1.2.1)</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <language></language>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
        <forum>http://www.hometheater.co.il/vt265959.html</forum>
        <source></source>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.profilecleaner" name="Profile Cleaner" version="1.0.4" provider-name="zeppy">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0" />
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="script.py">
		<provides>executable</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata" name="trakt.metadata">
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=264018</forum>
		<website>http://kodi.tv</website>
		<email></email>
		<source>https://github.com/cibboy/script.profilecleaner</source>
		<summary lang="en">Profile Cleaner cleans up your Kodi profile by deleting unused thumbnails, addon packages and addon settings</summary>
		<description lang="en">Profile Cleaner works by exclusion: the script reads the databases and excludes images and addons found. Once completed, the remaining images, addon packages and addon settings found in your profile will be deleted - or moved, according to your preference. Based on Max (m4x1m) Headroom's Thumbnails Cleaner.</description>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.subtitles.addic7ed.rvm"
  name="Addic7ed by Roman V.M."
  version="2.1.0"
  provider-name="Roman V.M.">
<requires>
  <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.19.0"/>
  <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4"/>
  <import addon="script.module.html5lib"/>
  <import addon="script.module.requests"/>
</requires>
<extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module" library="main.py" />
<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
  <summary lang="en">Addic7ed.com Subtitles</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">???????? Addic7ed.com</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">???????? Addic7ed.com</summary>
  <description lang="en">Subtitles service for Addic7ed.com.</description>
  <description lang="ru">?????? ????????? ??? ????? Addic7ed.com.</description>
  <description lang="uk">?????? ????????? ??? ????? Addic7ed.com.</description>
  <platform>all</platform>
</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.subtitles.addic7ed"
       name="Addic7ed.com"
       version="1.0.0"
       provider-name="CFlannagan">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.2.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module"
               library="service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Get subtitles from Addic7ed.com</summary>
        <description lang="en">Description for Addic7ed to come</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en"/>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <language/>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
        <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=184854</forum>
        <website/>
        <email/>
        <source>https://github.com/cflannagan/service.subtitles.addic7ed</source>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.subtitles.opensubtitles_by_opensubtitles"
       name="OpenSubtitles.org by OpenSubtitles"
       version="5.2.14"
       provider-name="amet, opensubtitles">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module"
             library="service.py" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary>OpenSubtitles by OpenSubtitles.org</summary>
    <description lang="en">Anonymously search and download subtitles for movies and TV-Series from OpenSubtitles.org without log-in. Search in 75 languages, 4.000.000+ subtitles, daily updates. </description>
	<description lang="at">Pelis and Subtitulos TV en munches llingues, milenta de subtitulos traducios y xubios caldia. Descarga llibre dende la fonte, sofitu API, millones d'usuarios.</description>
	<description lang="br">Istitlou Filmou ha TV e meur a yezh, miliadou a istitlou troet hag uskarget bemdez. Pellgargadenn digoust diouzh ar vammenn, skoazell an API, millionou a implijerien.</description>
	<description lang="ca">Subtitols de films i televisio en multiples idiomes, milers de subtitols traduits carregats diariament. Descarrega gratuita des de la font, suport de l'API, amb milions d'usuaris.</description>
	<description lang="cs">Titulky k filmum a serialum v mnoha jazycich, denne tisice nahranych prelozenych titulku. Stazeni zadarmo primo od zdroje, podpora API, miliony uzivatelu.</description>
	<description lang="de">Film- und TV-Untertitel in vielen Sprachen, taglicher Upload von tausenden ubersetzten Untertiteln. Freier Download von der Quelle, API-Unterstutzung, Millionen Nutzer</description>
	<description lang="el">Ôáéíßåò êáé ÓåéñÝò óå üëåò ôéò ãëþóóåò, ÷éëéÜäåò ìåôáöñáóìÝíïé õðüôéôëïé áíåâáßíïõí êáèçìåñéíÜ, êáôåâÜóôå äùñåÜí , õðïóôÞñéîç API áðü åêáôïììýñéá ÷ñÞóôåò</description>
	<description lang="eo">Filmaj kaj Televidaj subtekstoj en multaj lingvoj, miloj da tradukitaj subtekstoj ciutage alsutataj. Senpaga elsuto de fonto, API-subteno, miloj da uzantoj.</description>
	<description lang="es">Peliculas y Subtitulos en diversos idiomas, miles de subtitulos traducidos subidos diariamente. Descarge gratis, soporte API, millones de usuarios.</description>
	<description lang="et">Sadu Filmi ja TV Serjaalide subtiitrid erinevates keeltes laetakse ules igapaev. tasuta allalaadimine ja abi, rohkem kui miljon kasutajat.</description>
	<description lang="eu">Film eta Telebista azpitituluak hizkuntza anitzetan, milaka azpititulu itzuliak igotzen dira egunero. Doan jaitsi iturburutik, API sostengua, milioika erabiltzaile.</description>
	<description lang="fi">Tekstityksia useilla kielilla elokuviin ja TV-Sarjoihin, tuhansia uusia tekstityksia paivittain, ilmainen lataus, API tuki, miljoonia kayttajia.</description>
	<description lang="fr">Les sous-titres de film et telefilm en plusieurs langues, des milliers de sous-titres traduits tous les jours. Beneficiez de telechargements gratuits depuis la source, du support API, une d'une communaute de millions d'utilisateurs.</description>
	<description lang="hi">???? ?? ???? ???????? ?? ?????? ??? ?????? ???????? ?? ?????? ????? ????? ?? ??? ????? ??????? ????? ?? , ????? ??????, ???????????? ?? ????? ????? ?? ?</description>
	<description lang="hr">Titlovi za filmove i TV na mnogim jezicima, tisuce prijevoda postavljenih svaki dan. Besplatno preuzimanje s izvora, podrska za API, milijuni korisnika.</description>
	<description lang="hu">Film es TV feliratok tobb nyelven, naponta tobb ezer leforditott felirat feltoltes. Ingyenes letoltes a forrastol, API tamogatas, tobb millio felhasznalo.</description>
	<description lang="id">Subjudul film dan serial TV dalam multibahasa, ribuan subjudul diterjemah dan diunggah setiap harinya. Pengunduhan gratis dari sumber, didukung fitur antarmuka pemrograman aplikasi, dan jutaan pengguna.</description>
	<description lang="is">Textar fyrir myndir og sjonvarps?. a morgum tungumalum, ?usundir af ?yddum textum upphla?i? daglega. Fritt ni?urhal fra si?u, API stu?ningur, milljonir notenda.</description>
	<description lang="it">Sottotitoli di Film e TV in piu lingue,migliaia di sottotitoli tradotti caricati ogni giorno.Download gratuito,supporto API, milioni di utenti.</description>
	<description lang="ja">????????????????????????????????????????????????????????API ???????????????</description>
	<description lang="ka">?????????? ????????? ?? ??-????? ?????? ?????. ???????? ????????? ????????? ???????? ????????????. ????? ??????????? ????????, API ??????????, ?????????? ????????????</description>
	<description lang="km">???????????????? ??????????? ????????????????????? ????????????? ??????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????? ??????????????????????????? ?????? API ???????????????????????????????? </description>
	<description lang="ko">Movie and TV Subtitles in multiple languages, thousands of translated subtitles uploaded daily. Free download from source, API support, millions of users.</description>
	<description lang="ms">Sarikata TV dan Movie dalam pelbagai bahasa, ribuan terjemahan sarikata dimuat-naik setiap hari.Muat-turun percuma dari sumber utama, sokongan API, jutaan pengguna.</description>
	<description lang="nl">Ondertitels voor films en tv-series in meerdere talen, dagelijks upload van duizenden vertaalde ondertitels. Gratis downloaden van de bron, API ondersteuning, miljoenen gebruikers.</description>
	<description lang="no">Undertekster for film og TV pa mange sprak, med tusener av nye oversettelser hver dag. Vi har gratis nedlasting av undertekster, API-support, og mange millioner brukere.</description>
	<description lang="pt-br">Milhares de legendas para filmes e seriados de TV, em varios idiomas, sao traduzidas e enviadas diariamente. Download gratis, suporte API e milhoes de usuarios.</description>
	<description lang="pl">Napisy do filmow i seriali w wielu jezykach. Tysiace napisow dodawanych codziennie. Darmowe pobranie, miliony uzytkownikow.</description>
	<description lang="pt">Legendas de filmes e series de TV em varios idiomas, milhares de legendas traduzidas e enviadas diariamente. Download gratis a partir da fonte, suporte API, milhoes de utilizadores.</description>
	<description lang="ro">Subtitrari pentru filme in multe limbi, mii de subtitrari traduse si incarcate in fiecare zi. Descarca gratuit de la sursa, suport API, milioane de utilizatori.</description>
	<description lang="ru">???? ? ?? ???????? ?? ?????????? ??????, ?????? ????????????? ?????????? ????????? ?????????. ????????? ??????? ?? ???????? ???????, ????????? API, ???????? ?????????????.</description>
	<description lang="sk">Titulky pre filmy a TV serialy, denne nahratych tisice titulkov prelozenych vo viacerych jazykoch. Stahuj zadarmo zo zdroja, podpora API, miliony pouzivatelov.</description>
	<description lang="sl">Filmski in televizijski podnapisi v mnogo jezikih, na tisoce prevedenih podnapisov dnevno. Brezplacen prenos iz vira, podpora API, miljoni uporabnikov.</description>
	<description lang="sq">Titra filmash dhe serialesh ne shume gjuhe, mijera titra te perkthyera qe vendosen cdo dite. Shkarko nga burimi, apo nga mbeshtetja e API-se, miliona perdorues.</description>
	<description lang="sr">Titlovi za filmove i TV na mnogim jezicima, hiljade prevoda okacenih svakodnevno. Besplatno skidanje sa izvora, podrska za API, milioni korisnika.</description>
	<description lang="sv">Filmer och Tv-undertexter med olika sprak, tusentals oversatta undertexter uppladdade dagligen. Gratis nerladdning fran kallor, API support, miljoner av anvandare.</description>
	<description lang="tr">Her gun eklenen, pek cok dildeki binlerce film ve dizi altyaz?s?. Kaynag?ndan ucretsiz indirme, API destegi ve milyonlarca kullan?c?.</description>
	<description lang="uz">Film va TV Taglavhalari ko'p tillarda, minglab tarjima qilingan taglavhalar har kuni tizimga yuklanadi. Bepul resursdan yuklab oling, API qo'llaydi, millionlab foydalanuvchilar.</description>
	<description lang="zh">???????????,??????????????????,??API??,??????????</description>
    <disclaimer>Works without log-in</disclaimer>                                               
	<news>
Improved add-on by OpenSubtitles.org
v5.2.14 (2017-01-23)
- Users are able to download subtitles as anonymous without authentication. Added localized descriptions, media files
- New feature: Users are able to check for subtitles when Kodi is not playing, by using the manual search or by standing on an item and opening the subtitles search dialog (By key or by an external addon)  | @burekas
	</news>
    <platform>all</platform>
	<language></language>
    <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
    <forum>https://forum.opensubtitles.org/viewtopic.php?f=8&amp;t=15847</forum>
    <website>http://www.opensubtitles.org</website>
    <email>admin [at] opensubtitles {dot} org</email>                                               
	<assets>
	    <icon>resources/media/os_logo_512x512.png</icon>
	    <fanart>resources/media/os_fanart.jpg</fanart>    
		<screenshot>resources/media/screenshot_1.jpg</screenshot>
		<screenshot>resources/media/screenshot_2.jpg</screenshot>
		<screenshot>resources/media/screenshot_3.jpg</screenshot>				
	</assets>
    <source>https://github.com/opensubtitles/service.subtitles.opensubtitles_by_opensubtitles</source>    
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.subtitles.test" name="test" version="0.0.1" provider-name="none">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
		<import addon="repository.superrepo.org.helix.all" version="0.5.207" />
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module" library="service.py">
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">test</summary>
		<description lang="en">test</description>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<language>en</language>
		<forum></forum>
		<email></email>
	</extension>
</addon>

</addons>
